Hello and welcome. My name is Stephen Grider
Здравствуйте и добро пожаловать. Меня зовут Стивен Грайдер.
and I'm a member of Technical Staff at Anthropic. In
Я сотрудник технической команды Anthropic.
this course, we're going to get you up to speed with Claude Code. And
В этом курсе мы поможем вам уверенно начать работать с Claude Code.
before we get into anything too technical, I want to give you a
Но прежде чем переходить к техническим деталям, я хочу дать вам
quick overview on what we'll be learning. This
короткий обзор того, что мы будем изучать.
course is organized into four sections. We're
Этот курс разделён на четыре части.
going to first spend some time to understand exactly what
Сначала мы разберёмся, что именно собой представляет
a coding assistant is. We'll then take a look at Claude
ассистент для программирования. Затем рассмотрим Claude
Code itself and understand what makes it stand out among
Code и поймём, чем он выделяется среди
all the different coding assistants on the market.
других ассистентов для программирования на рынке.
Once we've established that, we'll walk through the use of Claude Code
После этого мы шаг за шагом разберём использование Claude Code
on a typical project and get some hands-on experience.
на типичном проекте и получим практический опыт.
Finally, we'll wrap things up by seeing how you can get the most
В завершение мы покажем, как извлечь максимум пользы
out of Claude Code on your own projects.
из Claude Code в ваших собственных проектах.